One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
The Tontatta Rebellion and
the C Block Finale!
Underneath Green Bit
Tontatta Kingdom
Underground?
That's right.
There is an underground passage between Green Bit and Dressrosa.
Here we are! The airport!
An army of bugs!
Tontatta Airport
Tontatta Airline
How cute!
This is Yellow Kabu 43. Ready to takeoff!
Yellow Kabu
(Great Golden Rhinoceros Beetle)
43, cleared for takeoff.
Pink Bee Squad, ready to go!
Pink Bee
(Pink Hornet)
Pink Bee, roger that.
All bugs, stand by and wait for further instruction.
Oh, Usoland, watch your step!
Sorry!
Kabu-san! Bian!
Leo, you're late!
Kabu: Captain of the Yellow Kabu Brigade
(User of the Incect Fruit, Model: Rhinoceros Beetle)
We're ready to go!
Bian: Captain of the Pink Bee Brigade
(User of the Incect Fruit, Model: Hornet)
We're going to fly at high speed!
I'll be counting on you two!
Leave it to us!
Our squad members have been training so hard for this day!
I've never seen this kind.
I want to show it to Luffy!
Usoland! Robiland!
You two are big so take the 20 passenger bus.
Come on, Linear Foxes!
20-Passenger Bus: Linear Fox
(Yelp Express)
This is nice! It's like a couch for a king!
They're fast when they run.
What gorgeous hair!
Alright, everybody! Let's get going!
With our hero Usoland!
To take back the 500 friends who are held captive!
Yeah!
I think I have to tell you two...
why we want to do this.
Where're you coming out from, old man?!
Gancho-san!
I'm the Tonta-chief, Gancho!
Thank you for this trip!
Alright!
Since you're going to fight and risk your lives,
you should know about this.
Well, I'm not willing to go that far...
Donquixote Doflamingo has been causing us, the Tontatta Tribe, a lot of pain recently.
But our connection with him goes way back
before the events of the last decade, actually.
It goes back about 900 years.
What?!
Here in Dressrosa, there is a vast sunflower field.
Somewhere in that field of blooming sunflowers, at a place no one knows,
there is a secret entrance.
Descend the stairs there,
and you will hear courageous voices.
Let me introduce you!
Commander!
We've been waiting for you, Commander!
Thanks, everyone!
Anti-Doflamingo Organization
"Riku Royal Army" Rebellion HQ
He looks like a strong toy-man!
What kind of Big Human was he?!
It's good to have him on the day of the battle!
We're going to fight with them!
They're Dwarves from the Tontatta Kingdom!
Dwarves?
They're as strong as you are.
They move faster than people can see them.
So they call them "fairies" in the town.
So the one who stole Zoro's sword was...
Quick!
Weren't you supposed to go back to your ship!?
Hey, don't let him attack you, Luffy!
Big Brother-san, I can't see!
Zoro!
Damn, that bastard!
Why didn't he tell me something like this was happening?!
I want to fight with my swords!
Oh, Commander!
Oh, Franky!
What are you doing here?
Commander, we have sorted out the intelligence from the scouting unit!
We know what the enemies and Sugar are doing.
And, no big surprise, with the battle close at hand...
That's right!
Some legendary heroes have appeared at Tontatta!
Their names are Usoland and Robiland!
They say they're on their way here!
On top of that, they have some friends with them.
Their names are:
Luffyland, Zoroland, Namiland, Sanland...
Chopperland, Fraland, and Boneland!
Must be Usopp!
Why did he tell such a lie?
Um, looks like I'm Zoroland.
I'm Fraland! Nice to meet you!
What?! That's awesome!
Oh, I don't have time for this!
I gotta get back to the Sunny!
Nami and the others are in danger!
What do you think I've been telling you?!
Coastal waters off Dressrosa
It's no use!
Art is unstoppable!
Blow Kung-Fu...
Art!
This is just smoke!
Here I go! Weather Egg!
Come on out, Snow Clouds!
Ew! Disgusting!
You turned my Clima Tact into a toy!
What an insult!
Who did you call a super model?!
I didn't say that!
"Turned it into a toy"? Don't confuse it with a toy!
You have no taste!
A devil fruit user that turns people into toys is within our family, but...
I'm an art-human who ate the Art Fruit!
You people have been turned into art!
Damn! Nami got defeated, too!
My antlers and hooves are useless!
Hey, Bone-kichi, she's trying to kidnap me!
I know! I'm not going to let her do it!
But look at this.
My Soul Solid looks like this!
Why are you whining like you're a victim?!
You should be happy that I made you artistic!
More importantly, look what you did to my submarine!
And to my men!
To avenge them,
what kind of artistic death should I bring to you?!
Hello? It's me! Who is this?!
We're in big trouble right now! Help us!
Who said you could pick that up?!
Is this Tony-ya?!
I don't care what's going on over there!
Listen carefully!
What?! Is this Tra-guy?!
Is that Law?
What are you doing, Tra-guy?! Come to the ship right now!
We got turned into art! Help us!
I-I'm just fine!
Listen, I need you to...
sail the ship to Green Bit now!
I want to leave Caesar with you guys!
Whaat?! He asked us the impossible and hung up!
I thought he already handed Caesar-san over!
What's wrong with him?!
He just talked without hearing what we had to say!
Is he Luffy?!
Green Bit
It's no use, Law!
Who did you call just now?
Give me back Caesar's heart already.
It's so meaningless for you to keep hanging on here.
Your partner, Straw Hat, has already walked into the trap that I set up.
He's now fighting in the gladiatorial contest at the Colosseum.
Tough contenders from all over the world
come to fight in that outlaws-only, deadly competition.
When someone loses, it's a one-way ticket to hell.
He'll never make it out of the Colosseum alive.
Your alliance is over.
Law...
give up!
Dressrosa
Sanji and Kin'emon
Go! Luffy-dono!
Why're you cheering with the others?!
But, Sanji-dono, when a man fights, he has to win!
Burgess!
I heard that it's getting interesting!
Who's the shrimp?
Rubber...
Hawk Rifle!
Lucy's going for it!
You're quite a fighter.
I can't get beaten by you here!
That's a joke! You have no chance!
They lionized you squirts by calling you all "The Worst Generation", and it looks like it emboldened you.
But you guys aren't strong enough to go across the sea that we fought on.
Without Whitebeard, we can't expect too much from the next generation.
The only guy who looks good is Blackbeard Teach!
Blackbeard?
If I had to pick one, it's him. But anyway,
if you're only good enough to compete against me in my present condition, your hopeless!
Just give up being a pirate!
You're not half bad, but if Rayleigh chose a brat
of this level as the flag-bearer for the new generation,
he's not as bright as he used to be!
The Marines showed some good insight when they squelched the most evil of the lot,
I mean Ace, of course, in the war two years ago.
That fool had the demon's blood in his veins!
You think you can beat the Marine admirals and the Four Emperors, and surpass Roger?!
That's absolutely impossible!
Rubber...
Rocket!
Lucy is flying?!
That's an incredibly high jump!
Come on! I'm going to teach you a lesson!
With 30 years worth of focused anger, I'm going all out, Straw Hat Luffy!
What the hell is with this ice?!
We can't break it with fire or an axe!
But under the ice you can see all this pirate treasure!
This continent is made of what they call "Crystal Ice Sheet", and to break it,
you have to put tremendous amount of pressure on one spot!
Drilling Dragon Auger Spike!
Open, Chinjao!
Did you fellows like that?
Hey, tie those treasure thieves up and dump them into the sea!
Okay, Boss!
True happiness!
Happo Pirate Navy's 12th Leader
Chinajo the Auger (30 Years Ago)
This room of ice contains everything of my life.
Joys and sorrows from the past.
Hopes for the future.
Several decades worth of my family's treasures!
My drill head is the only key to the room.
Nobody can invade this place! Not even the Marines!
Hey, Chinjao! I'm going to break that head of yours today.
As preparation, I put aside the punching bag and trained by reducing eight mountains to dust.
No matter what you do, it's no use!
There is not a thing in the world harder than my head!
Prepare yourself, Chinjao!
I'm going to break that fist you're so proud of, Garp!
Boss!
He did it!
Retreat!
All ships, set sail!
Boss!
Boss! I'm glad that you're okay!
Open Chinjao!
Drilling Dragon Auger Spike!
Boss!
Please stop, Boss!
You're going to die!
Open!
It won't open.
What should I do?! Those are my treasures!
I can see them right there! There's everything of my life!
My fortune!
Damn you, Garp! I'll never forgive you!
I will carry this grudge towards your children and your children's children, Garp!
I am...
cursing you and will hold it forever!
A short time later, I retired from pirating.
I lost my power and my heart was broken.
What's that?!
Am I hallucinating!? It seems like...
Lucy's arm has become gigantic!
Watch what I'm going to do, Garp!
I'm going to kill your precious grandson!
Pay for it!
Your old man's punch took everything away from me!
Stop whining over one punch!
I can't count how many times he punched me!
I'm going to smash all of your bones to pieces!
Eight Impact Fist Secret Technique...
Rubber...
Thor...
Drill-less Dragon's...
Elephant Gun!
Drill-less Bit!
Whaat?!
Old man!
Grandpa!
Oh, ring out!
Chinjao was eliminated by being thrown out of the ring!
What a man!
The one who beat a legend and won the fierce fight of Block C is...
Lucy the Gladiator!
Yeah!
Lucy! Lucy! Lucy!
I didn't expect him to go this far, that Lucy!
It's really a surprising ending!
Cut the "Lucy" crap!
Those cheers are irritating!
He's that popular even while using a fake name!
Just come back here already!
I'm not going to let you get away this time, Straw Hat!
Didn't you hear what I said before?
I'm not going to let you kill him.
Cavendish!
If you get in my way, I'm going to kill you, too, Bartolomeo!
Fine by me!
I'm going to kill Straw Hat!
Straw Hat?
How interesting!
So that's how it is!